https://www.madisonphotoworks.com/privacy_policy.php

Easy Link ROES / Order On Line      Quick Order
Support      Where We Are Located      Sign Up For Our Newsletter
Privacy Policy
We at Nu Imaging Professional and our affiliated companies are committed to
respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection
and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information")
you share with us.
Nu Imaging Professional has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can
understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.
Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an
individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or
other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether
at work or at home. In general, you can visit our Web pages without telling
us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.
If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on the Web, we may
transfer that Information within Nu Imaging Professional or to our third-party service
providers, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries
or jurisdictions around the world.
Nu Imaging Professional strives to comply with all applicable laws around the
globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements
may vary from country to country, Nu Imaging Professional intends to adhere
to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy even if, in connection
with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries
that may not require an "adequate" level of protection for your Personal
Information. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal
Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred,
or retained.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies.
A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to
collect information about Web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies
may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user.
Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept
them and how to remove them.
You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may
choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose
to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user
ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Web site.
Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host
names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system
types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed.
Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our
Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does
not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.
To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following principles:
Notice
Where Nu Imaging Professional collects Personal Information on the web, we
intend to post a purpose statement that explains why Personal Information will
be collected and whether we plan to share such Personal Information outside
of Nu Imaging Professional or those working on Nu Imaging Professional's behalf.
Nu Imaging Professional does not intend to transfer Personal Information without
your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Nu Imaging Professional Name
's behalf unless such transfer is legally required.
Choice
You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Nu Imaging Professional
Name . The notice we intend to provide where Nu Imaging Professional collects
Personal Information on the Web should help you to make this choice. If you
choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit
most of Nu Imaging Professional's Web sites, but you may be unable to access
certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you.
If you chose to have a relationship with Nu Imaging Professional, such as a
contractual or other business relationship or partnership, we will naturally
continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship.
Security
Wherever your Personal Information may be held within Nu Imaging Professional
or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect
the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or
disclosure.
Access/Accuracy
To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Nu Imaging Professional
Name
wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect
Personal Information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of
contacting Nu Imaging Professional should you need to update or correct that
Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible,
you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information to [
Company E-mail
and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the
changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.
Third Party Services
Third parties provide certain services available on nuimagingpro.com website
on
Nu Imaging Professional's behalf. Nu Imaging Professional may provide information,
including Personal Information, that Nu Imaging Professional collects on the
Web to third-party service providers to help us deliver programs, products,
information, and services. Service providers are also an important means by
which Nu Imaging Professional maintains its Web site and mailing lists. Nu Imaging Professional will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party
service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on Nu Imaging Professional
Name 's behalf.
Nu Imaging Professional does not intend to transfer Personal Information without
your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Nu Imaging Professional
's behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against
Nu Imaging Professional's policy to sell Personal Information collected online
without consent.
Children's Privacy
Nu Imaging Professional' website
is not structured to attract children. Accordingly,
we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under
13 years of age.
Commitment
If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy,
please contact us at support@nuimagingpro.com. While we cannot guarantee privacy
perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as
possible.
Your Consent
By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy
and to Nu Imaging Professional' processing of Personal Information for the
purposes given above as well as those explained where Nu Imaging Professional
collects Personal Information on the Web. Should the Online Privacy Policy change,
we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought
to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable
period of time.
